def dog_mode
  # question_styleは 2：選択形式
    
  # {question: "出題内容", answer: "正回答", dummy1: "誤回答", dummy2: "誤回答", answer_num: question:を除いて、正回答は左から何番目か},
    [
      {question: "犬のクイズ", answer: "犬ちゃん", dummy1: "猫", dummy2: "鳥", answer_num: 1},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "猫ちゃん", answer: "犬", dummy2: "鳥", answer_num: 2},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "鳥ちゃん", dummy2: "猫", answer: "犬", answer_num: 3},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", answer: "犬ちゃん", dummy1: "猫", dummy2: "鳥", answer_num: 1},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "猫ちゃん", answer: "犬", dummy2: "鳥", answer_num: 2},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "鳥ちゃん", dummy2: "猫", answer: "犬", answer_num: 3},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", answer: "犬ちゃん", dummy1: "猫", dummy2: "鳥", answer_num: 1},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "猫ちゃん", answer: "犬", dummy2: "鳥", answer_num: 2},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "鳥ちゃん", dummy2: "猫", answer: "犬", answer_num: 3},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", answer: "犬ちゃん", dummy1: "猫", dummy2: "鳥", answer_num: 1},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", answer: "犬ちゃん", dummy1: "猫", dummy2: "鳥", dummy3: "鳥", answer_num: 1},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "猫ちゃん", answer: "犬", dummy2: "鳥", dummy3: "鳥", answer_num: 2},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "鳥ちゃん", dummy2: "猫", answer: "犬", dummy3: "鳥", answer_num: 3},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "鳥ちゃん", dummy2: "猫", dummy3: "犬", answer: "鳥", answer_num: 4},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", answer: "犬ちゃん", dummy1: "猫", dummy2: "鳥", dummy3: "鳥", answer_num: 1},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "猫ちゃん", answer: "犬", dummy2: "鳥", dummy3: "鳥", answer_num: 2},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "鳥ちゃん", dummy2: "猫", answer: "犬", dummy3: "鳥", answer_num: 3},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "鳥ちゃん", dummy2: "猫", dummy3: "犬", answer: "鳥", answer_num: 4},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", answer: "犬ちゃん", dummy1: "猫", dummy2: "鳥", dummy3: "鳥", answer_num: 1},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "猫ちゃん", answer: "犬", dummy2: "鳥", dummy3: "鳥", answer_num: 2},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "鳥ちゃん", dummy2: "猫", answer: "犬", dummy3: "鳥", answer_num: 3},
      {question: "犬のクイズ", dummy1: "鳥ちゃん", dummy2: "猫", dummy3: "犬", answer: "鳥", answer_num: 4}
    ]
end